[Apocalypse Log 2]
You...
Who are you?
What did you do to me?
I'm your savior.
If it weren't for me, you'd be dead.
I'm the one who bandaged your wounds.
If I wanted to hurt you,
I wouldn't have waited until now.
I didn't need you to save me.
What's your motive for saving me?
What motive could I have?
Even if it were a wounded kitten or puppy,
I'd save it if I could.
Let alone a living person like you.
Don't think you can
get any information from me.
I'll just assume your brain is damaged, too.
I won't hold it against you.
Since I've brought you back,
I'll take responsibility for you.
Don't worry.
This is my secret camp.
No one else will come here.
It's easy to die in the apocalypse.
If you really didn't want to live...
then how did you get these injuries?
We're running out of food.
You two should discuss it the next few days.
It's time to head out.
Now that we have new equipment,
maybe we can go farther
and find some good stuff.
Yeah.
This hunting bow is very powerful.
It'd be great if we all had one.
All right. I'll look into it later.
Perfect.
Before we leave, I'll go reinforce the traps.
Then I'll find some wild fruits
for Grandma Qiu.
I won't be back for lunch.
I've brought some dry rations.
Okay. Li Ming and I will work on the plan.
We'll set out in three days.
Sure.
Be careful out there.
It's not poison.
See for yourself.
It's real anti-inflammatory medicine.
Fine.
Let me check your wounds
and change your bandages first.
How did you get all these injuries?
How did you end up in the woods?
I was passing by while searching for supplies.
I ran into a horde of zombies.
I didn't expect a camp to be nearby.
Then you're quite lucky.
You ran into me.
Barely.
How long has this camp been established?
This place...
We all searched for a long time
before deciding on it.
This area is easy to defend but hard to attack.
Your companions are quite capable.
Everyone gives their all to survive.
I've also researched many safety measures.
I even intercepted three zombies yesterday.
You're quite desperate to survive, too.
You must really want to live.
So, why didn't you ask me for help?
Instead, you tried to drive me away.
Who knew if you wanted to hurt or save me?
Now, you know I'm not a bad person, right?
Don't move.
The wound is still a little inflamed.
You need anti-inflammatory meds to heal faster.
That's more like it.
Why make things hard for yourself?
Let go.
Let go!
What are you doing?
To survive in this apocalypse,
you must be wary of more than just zombies.
I can tell who's good and who's bad.
I know you're not a bad person.
But you're not a good one either.
No dinner for you tonight.
Get some rest and recover.
What a jerk.
All he does is talk tough.
This time, we're going
to the school in the east.
Lin Zai.
Are you sure there are still supplies there?
Yes.
But we were attacked by zombies back then.
The nearby areas have been picked clean.
We have to take the risk this time.
All right.
I remember the layout of the school.
But we still have to be extremely careful.
I've prepared everything we need.
I've also reinforced and checked
the traps around the camp.
Grandma Qiu's safety is guaranteed.
Okay, let's head out immediately.
If anything unusual happens,
withdraw immediately.
Okay.
Are there zombies?
You're not dead.
I'm here to take back my things.
Sorry.
Finders keepers. It's ours now.
Don't come any closer.
Don't move. Stay back.
Return my backpack exactly as it was.
I know you won't hurt me.
I won't hurt any of you.
As long as you return what's mine.
But if you refuse,
you're forcing my hand.
Give it all back to him.
What is this junk?
The watch on your wrist is mine, too.
It was my idea to take your things.
But I also saved your life.
Let's call it even.
You can go.
Guang Qi.
Calling HQ.
Signal lost.
Unable to establish a stable connection.
Check operational status of other core modules.
Network unavailable.
Location module precision dropping.
Physiological module
detected surface trauma on user,
and signs of mild infection.
Sample Escort Protocol updated.
Immune target confirmed.
[Quanhe School]
Chen.
Li.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lied to you.
But I really didn't know he would turn on us.
It's all my fault.
You can hit me if you want.
Let's forget about it this time.
We checked him that day.
That man really hadn't been bitten by a zombie.
But we still left him for dead.
We really didn't have to be so heartless.
We could have left him some food and medicine.
Lin Zai, you did the right thing.
This incident serves as a reminder to us.
We strive to survive, not just so we can live,
but so that all of humanity can survive.
If you must apologize,
then carry more supplies.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm not helping you this time.
I'm good.
Li, I just saw a few bottles
of the hard liquor you like.
I'll carry a few for you to make it up to you.
All right!
Two bottles at most.
Prioritize the essential supplies.
I know.
Mind your own business.
Run!
Guys, run!